fliptopia.com 2017-06-23

# Fliptopia

### Privacy Policy

* * *

Thank you for your interest in Fliptopia.com and Fliptopia.net, a service provided to you by Apptopia, Inc. This Website and any other URLs and Websites administered by Apptopia, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, the “Website”) are offered by Apptopia, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, “Apptopia” or “we” or “us”) to you, the user, subject to your acceptance of the Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. The terms “you” and “user” refers to all individuals and entities that access the Website(s). Please contact us at [support@apptopia.com](mailto:support@apptopia.com) with any questions regarding this Agreement. BY USING THIS SERVICE, YOU AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS AGREEMENT AND AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. It is the responsibility of all users to revisit this page to check for changes. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before accessing or using the Website. By accessing or using any part of the Website, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, then you may not access the Website or use any services.

By using the Website, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, scraping, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S., your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Website and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to and processing in the US.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [support@apptopia.com](mailto:support@apptopia.com)

#### Information Collected Upon Registration and Adding Social Media Accounts.

In order to access some functionality of the Website, you are required to become a registered user and to submit certain personally identifiable information to the Website. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for our services, make a purchase or sale, or engage in other present and future Website interactions. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your IP address, full name, business name, user name, password, email address, city, time zone, and other information that you decide to provide us with, or that information that you allow us to collect at the time of integrating a widget, a social media account, or any applicable third party software account.

#### Use of Contact Information.

In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to services on the Website. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or in the My Account or My Fliptopia locations on the Website.

#### Log Data.

When you visit the Website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, and the messages you create and share within the Website. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider, the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Website and of our Services, and for the Website's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except as required to enforce this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use for the Website or as necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of Apptopia, its employees, customers, or other users.

#### Aggregate Information.

Certain information is used in the aggregate to provide analytics to Apptopia. This information is not tied to you personally but may contain demographic information about the users in part or as a whole. This aggregate and non-personally identifiable information may be used by Apptopia and shared with or sold to third parties.

#### Third Party Account Access.

In order to access certain information required to facilitate the sale of any application or product uploaded on the Website by any user, including the statistics available on third party sites, i.e. download data and sales information from app stores. By uploading an application or product for sale, user agrees to provide us with access to those third party accounts and grants permission to Apptopia to gather information from those third party sites concerning the applicable application or product and featuring such information on the Website listing, in marketing and/or promotional materials, and in any such other format that Apptopia may utilize in order to promote the Website and/or the application or product.

#### Personal Information Accessible by Other Users.

By becoming a registered user and engaging in sales transactions on the Website, you authorize us to make your personal information in the form of your name, business information, and contact information (in the form of your email address and mailing address) available to the other user in the transaction in part to facilitate the sale, asset transfer, and communication.

#### Cookies. 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user returns. Fliptopia uses cookies to help Apptopia identify and track users, their usage of the Website, and their website access preferences. Users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Website, with the drawback that certain features of the Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure. 

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, billing services, software review services, customer relationship management, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

#### Business Transfers. 

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of Apptopia’s assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### Security. 

We believe in the privacy of our website users. We safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Website in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

#### Payment. 

Our shopping cart is powered by Merchant Warehouse, founded in 1998 and based in Boston, Massachusetts.  The company’s ecommerce platform is PCI compliant adhering to standards and protocols for building and maintaining secure networks for financial transactions. Through Merchant Warehouse, we accept MasterCard, Visa, American Express and Discover.  For more information on Merchant Warehouse’s security and privacy policies [click here](http://authorize.net/). Users will submit their credit card or other banking information in their account, which will be kept on file by Merchant Warehouse for user’s future transactions on the Website. 

We use Heartland Payment Systems, Inc. as our merchant gateway to process all credit card transactions.   Located in Missouri, Heartland Payment Systems, Inc. was founded in 1997.   Heartland Payment Systems, Inc. has its own privacy policy regarding how they collect and use your information and what you can do to restrict that.  Click here to review their privacy statement. 

#### Links to Other Websites. 

The Website, any communications from Apptopia, and messages posted through the Website may contain links or references to other websites. The Website cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the content that appears on those sites, and our posting of or reference to any such content is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. Furthermore, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party site or for how they treat information about their users. These third party sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information. You may be consenting to those websites through use of ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements and terms of service for each of the other websites you visit.

#### Our Policy Towards Children

The Website is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [Support@apptopia.com](mailto:Support@apptopia.com). We will take actions to promptly remove such data. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.
